Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art financial records, 1872-1988 COR0004.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Receipts & disbursements, 1870-1884, 1919-1935, 1940-1948; Series 9
  - Receipt numbers 6801-6810, 1920 October-November; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Receipt numbers 6811-6825, 1920 November-1921 January; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Receipt numbers 6826-6850, 1921 January-April; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Receipt numbers 6851-6855, 1921 April-May; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Receipt numbers 6856-6875, 1921 May-July; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Receipt numbers 6876-6900, 1921 August-December; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Receipt numbers 6901-6925, 1921 December-1922 February; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Receipt numbers 6926-6950, 1922 February-May; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Receipt numbers 6951-6960, 1922 May-June; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Receipt numbers 6961-6975, 1922 June-August; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Receipt numbers 6976-6990, 1922 September-October; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Receipt numbers 6991-7000, 1922 November-December; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Receipt numbers 7001-7010, 1922 December-1923 January; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Receipt numbers 7011-7030, 1922 December-1923 April; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Receipt numbers 7031-7040, 1923 March-May; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Receipt numbers 7041-7060, 1923 May-July; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Receipt numbers 7061-7080, 1923 June-September; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Receipt numbers 7081-7100, 1923 September-December; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Receipt numbers 7101-7125, 1923 December-1924 January; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Receipt numbers 7126-7140, 1924 January-March; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Receipt numbers 7141-7165, 1924 March-May; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Receipt numbers 7166-7175, 1924 April-June; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Receipt numbers 7176-7200, 1924 June-October; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Receipt numbers 7201-7220, 1924 November-1925 January; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Receipt numbers 7221-7240, 1925 January-April; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Receipt numbers 7241-7255, 1925 April-May; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Receipt numbers 7256-7275, 1925 May-July; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Receipt numbers 7276-7300, 1925 July-October; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Receipt numbers 7301-7323, 1925 October-1926 January; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Receipt numbers 7324-7335, 1926 January-March; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Receipt numbers 7335-7365, 1926 March-May; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Receipt numbers 7366-7380, 1926 June-July; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Receipt numbers 7381-7400, 1926 July-September; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Receipt numbers 7401-7425, 1926 October-December; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Receipt numbers 7426-7445, 1927 January-March; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Receipt numbers 7446-7475, 1927 April-June; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Receipt numbers 7476-7500, 1927 July-September; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Receipt numbers 7501-7525, 1927 September-November; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Receipt numbers 7526-7550, 1927 November-December; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Receipt numbers 7551-7564, 1928 January-February; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Receipt numbers 7565-7585, 1928 February-March; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Receipt numbers 7586-7600, 1928 March-April; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Receipt numbers 7601-7620, 1928 April-May; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Receipt numbers 7621-7650, 1928 May-July; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Receipt numbers 7651-7675, 1928 July-October; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Receipt numbers 7676-770, 1928 October-December; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Receipt numbers 7701-7720, 1928 December-1929 February; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Receipt numbers 7721-7725, 1929 February-March; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Receipt numbers 7726-7740, 1929 March-May; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Receipt numbers 7741-7760, 1929 May-June; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Receipt numbers 7761-7775, 1929 June-August; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Receipt numbers 7776-7800, 1929 August-November; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Receipt numbers 7801-7815, 1929 November-December; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Receipt numbers 7816-7835, 1929 December-1930 March; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Receipt numbers 7836-7860, 1930 March-May; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Receipt numbers 7861-7875, 1930 May-June; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Receipt numbers 7876-7900, 1930 June-August; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Receipt numbers 7901-7925, 1930 September-November; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Receipt numbers 7926-7950, 1930 December-1931 February; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Receipt numbers 7951-7975, 1931 February-April; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Receipt numbers 7976-8000, 1931 May-July; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Receipt numbers 8001-8025, 1931 July-October; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Receipt numbers 8026-8050, 1931 November-1932 February; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Receipt numbers 8051-8075, 1932 February-May; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Receipt numbers 8076-8100, 1932 May-July; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Receipt numbers 8101-8125, 1932 August-November; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Receipt numbers 8126-8150, 1932 November-1933 January; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Receipt numbers 8151-8175, 1933 January-April; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Receipt numbers 8176-8200, 1933 April-July; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Receipt numbers 8201-8220, 1933 July-October; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Receipt numbers 8221-8235, 1933 October-December; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Receipt numbers 8236-8250, 1933 November-December; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Receipt numbers 8251-8275, 1933 December-1934 March; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Receipt numbers 8276-8300, 1934 March-June; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Receipt numbers 8301-8325, 1934 June-September; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Receipt numbers 8351-8375, 1934 December-1935 March; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - [Receipts and Disbursements], 1940 June-October; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - [Receipts and Disbursements], 1940 November-December; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - [Receipts and Disbursements], 1941 January-March; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - [Receipts and Disbursements], 1941 April-June; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - [Receipts and Disbursements], 1941 July-September; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - [Receipts and Disbursements], 1941 October-December; Series 9 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - [Receipts and Disbursements], 1942 January-December; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 1-4)
  - [Receipts and Disbursements], 1943 January-December; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 5-8)
  - [Receipts and Disbursements], 1944 January-December; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 9-12)
  - [Receipts and Disbursements], 1945 January-December; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 13-16)
  - [Receipts and Disbursements], 1946 January-December; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 17-20)
  - [Receipts and Disbursements], 1947 January-April; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Receipt numbers 9901 - 9925, 1947 May-June; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Receipt numbers 9926 - 9950, 1947 July-October; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Receipt numbers 9951 - 9975, 1947 October-December; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Receipt numbers 9976 - 9980, 1947 December; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Receipt numbers 9981 - 9985, 1947 December; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Receipt numbers 9986 - 10000, 1947 December-1948 February; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Receipt numbers 10001 - 10025, 1948 February-March; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Receipt numbers 10026 - 10040, 1948 March-May; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Receipt numbers 10041 - 10055, 1948 April-May; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Receipt numbers 10056 - 10065, 1948 May-June; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Receipt numbers 10066 - 10074, 1948 June; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - [Receipts and Disbursements], 1948 July-December; Series 9 (Box 17, Folder 33-36)
- Bequests, 1936-1972; Series 10
  The series is arranged by bequest and, thereafter, chronologically.
  Researchers should use these records in conjunction with the Bequest Series in the Registrar's Office Records (RG 5).
  Contains correspondence, drafts of deeds of gift, memoranda, reports, and stock statements concerning the James Parmelee Bequest (1940) and the Edith G. Halpert Bequest (1965-Revoked 1968). The Parmelee materials concern accounts of annual profits to the Corcoran from Parmelee stocks. The Halpert files document the Corcoran's efforts to negotiate a suitable agreement with Mrs. Halpert in bequeathing her modern art collection to the Corcoran.
  - James Parmelee, 1936; Series 10 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - James Parmelee, 1937 June-December; Series 10 (Box 17, Folders 38-39)
  - James Parmelee, 1938; Series 10 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - James Parmelee, 1939; Series 10 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - James Parmelee, 1940 January-December; Series 10 (Box 17, Folders 42-43)
  - James Parmelee, 1941 January-December; Series 10 (Box 17, Folders 44-47)
  - James Parmelee, 1942-1949; Series 10 (Box 17, Folders 48-55)
  - James Parmelee, 1950-1955; Series 10 (Box 17, Folders 56-61)
  - James Parmelee, 1956-1959; Series 10 (Box 18, Folders 1-4)
  - James Parmelee, 1960-1961; Series 10 (Box 18, Folders 5-6)
  - James Parmelee, 1967-1968; Series 10 (Box 18, Folders 7-8)
  - James Parmelee, 1971-1972; Series 10 (Box 18, Folders 9-10)
  - Edith Halpert, 1960; Series 10 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Edith Halpert, 1961 January-December; Series 10 (Box 18, Folders 12-16)
  - Edith Halpert, 1942 January; Series 10 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Edith Halpert, 1962 February; Series 10 (Box 18, Folders 18-19)
  - Edith Halpert (Drafts of Agreement of Gift), 1962 February; Series 10 (Box 18, Folders 20-21)
  - Edith Halpert, 1962 March-December; Series 10 (Box 18, Folders 22-25)
  - Edith Halpert, 1963; Series 10 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Edith Halpert, 1964 January-August; Series 10 (Box 18, Folders 27-28)
  - Edith Halpert (Drafts of Agreement of Gift), 1964 August; Series 10 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Edith Halpert, 1964 October-December; Series 10 (Box 18, Folders 30-31)
  - Edith Halpert, 1965; Series 10 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Edith Halpert (Revoked Nov. 1, 1968), 1966; Series 10 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Exhibition expenses, 1949-1982; Series 11
  Materials are arranged chronologically by exhibition date.
  Researchers should use this series in conjunction with the exhibition expense ledgers in Series I in this record group. In addition, the exhibition files in the Curatorial Records (RG 5) should be checked as they most likely contain exhibition expense/budget information.
  Contains correspondence, exhibition budget statements, memoranda, and some receipts/invoices concerning numerous Corcoran exhibitions including the American Processional (Sesquicentennial Exhibit) (1950), Area Shows, and Corcoran Biennials.
  - 21st Biennial, 1949 March 27-May 8; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - American Processional - Bills, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - American Processional - Budgets 1948-49, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - American Processional - Budgets 1950, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - American Processional - Budgets 1950-51, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - American Processional - Contracts with Commission of Fine Arts, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - American Processional - Installation Plan, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - American Processional - Insurance, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - American Processional - Personnel, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folders 42-44)
  - American Processional - Progress Reports, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - American Processional - Renovations: Curtains, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - American Processional - Renovations: Door Installation, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - American Processional - Renovations: Painting, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - American Processional - Renovations: Step Rails, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - American Processional - Renovations: Venetian Blinds, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - American Processional, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - American Processional - Travel Expenses, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folders 52-53)
  - American Processional - Vouchers, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - American Processional - Vouchers 1-15, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - American Processional - Vouchers 16-30, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - American Processional - Vouchers 31-50, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - American Processional - Vouchers 51-65, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - American Processional - Vouchers 66-80, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - American Processional - Vouchers 81-103, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - American Processional - Miscellaneous, 1950 July 8-December 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folders 61-62)
  - Area Show - 5th, 1951 January 28-March 4; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Biennial - 22nd, 1951 March 31-May 13; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Area Show - 6th, 1951 November 25-1952 January 20; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Miscellaneous, 1951; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Privately Owned, 1952 February 10-March 30; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - John Sloan, 1952 March 16-April 20; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Area Show - 7th, 1952 November 23-1953 January 18; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Biennial - 23rd, 1953 March 15-May 3; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - Area Show - 8th, 1953 November 22-1954 January 3; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Miscellaneous, 1954; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Area Show - 9th, 1955 January 8-February 13; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - Biennial - 24th, 1955 March 13-May 8; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Family of Man, 1955 July 1-July 31; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Area Show - 10th, 1955 December 2-1956 February 5; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Area Show - 11th, 1956 December 2-1957 January 20; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Miscellaneous, 1956; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Biennial - 25th, 1957 January 13-March 10; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - Area Show - 12th, 1957 November 22-1958 January 5; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - Miscellaneous, 1957; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - Area Show - 13th, 1958 November 21-December 14; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 82)
  - Miscellaneous, 1958; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 83)
  - Biennial 26th, 1959 January 16-March 8; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 84)
  - Masterpieces of the CGA, 1959 January 29-March 7; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 85)
  - American Muse, 1959 April 3-May 17; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 86)
  - Miscellaneous, 1959; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 87)
  - Miscellaneous, 1960; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 88)
  - Biennial - 27th, 1961 January 13-February 26; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 89)
  - Faberge Easter Eggs, 1961 March 10-September 3; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 90)
  - Norwegian Exhibition, 1961 October 5-November 5; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 91)
  - Civil War, 1961 November 17-December 31; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 92)
  - Miscellaneous, 1961; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 93)
  - Area Show - 15th, 1962 January 19-February 18; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 94)
  - John Marin, 1962 March 2-April 15; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 95)
  - William Ranney, 1962 October 4-November 11; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 96)
  - 16 German Artists - Correspondence, 1962 November 27-December 30; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 97)
  - 16 German Artists - Receipts, 1962 November 27-December 30; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 98)
  - 16 German Artists - Travelling Show, 1962 November 27-December 30; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 99)
  - Miscellaneous, 1962; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 100)
  - Biennial - 28th, 1963 January 19-March 3; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 101)
  - Stephen Greene - Travelling Show, 1963 March 14-April 14; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 102)
  - Contemporary Painting in Belgium, 1963 October 3-December 1; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 103)
  - Area Show - 16th, 1963 December 12-1964 February 2; Series 11 (Box 18, Folder 104)
  - Miscellaneous, 1963; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Gabor Peteroi - Traveling Show, 1964 February 3-March 29; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - John Singer Sargent - Traveling Show, 1964 April 17-June 14; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Japanese Exhibition, 1964 October 1-November 29; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1964; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Kreeger Collection, 1965 February 19-March 28; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Childe Hassam, 1965 May 1-August 1; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Area show - 17th, 1965 November 12-December 19; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Contemporary Trenos, 1966 January 7-February 13; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Yugoslavia - Contemporary Trends, 1966 January 7-February 13; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Peruvian Painting and Sculpture, 1966 October 28-December 18; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, 1966; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Biennial - 30th, 1967 February 24-April 19; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Australian Painters, 1967 March 10-April 16; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Richard Woodville, 1967 April 21-June 11; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Jules Olitski, 1967 April 28-June 11; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous, 1967; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Sweden Today, 1968 January 18-March 3; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous, 1968; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Biennial - 31st - Catalog Dispute, 1969 February 1-March 16; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - David Smith, 1969 October 17-December 7; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous, 1969; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - American Genre Painting (Cancelled by 1970), Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Paolo Soleri - Catalog and HUD Grant, 1970 February 21-April 5; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Paolo Soleri - Correspondence, etc., 1970 February 21-April 5; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Paolo Soleri - Correspondence, etc., 1970 February 21-April 5; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Alexander Liberman, 1970 April 19-May 31; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Eleanor Dickinson, 1970 September 25-November 1; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - New Sculpture, 1970 October 9-November 15; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous, 1970; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Biennial - 32nd, 1971 February 28-April 4; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Thomas Wilfred, 1971 April 17-May 30; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous, 1971; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Albert Bierstadt, 1972 April 7-May 14; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Joseph Akston, 1972 May 6-May 28; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous, 1972; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous, 1974; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Frymire (Jacob) - Catalog Dispute, 1975 October 4-November 16; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous, 1975; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous, 1977; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Honore Daumier, 1979 September 21-December 18; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Northern Light, 1982 September 11-October 17; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 42)
- Art rental and gift shop, 1949-1980; Series 12
  Other archival records to check include the separate record groups on the Art Rental Gallery (RG 3) and the Corcoran Shop (RG 6). In addition, Series I in these records should be investigated for ledgers with pertinent information.
  Includes art rental policy statements, correspondence, inventories & lists, memoranda, damage to works of art reports, rental receipts, and D.C. sales tax quarterly and annual reports. The series documents the financial aspects of both the Art Rental Gallery, which opened 9 March 1962, and the Corcoran Shop. Sales & Use tax reports make up the bulk of the series.
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1949; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1950; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1951; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1952; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1953; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1954; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1955; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1956; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1957; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1958; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1959; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1960; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Sales Desk Report, 1960; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1961; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Sales Desk Report, 1961; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1962; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Sales Desk and Art Rental Report, 1962; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Art Rental Reports, 1963; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1963; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Art Rental - Damages - Will Barnett Dark Image II, 1964; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Art Rental Reports, 1964; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1964; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1965; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1966; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Art Rental Reports, 1967; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1967; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Art Rental Reports, 1968; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Sales Desk Report, 1968; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1968; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Art Rental Policy, 1969; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Art Rental Reports, 1969; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Sales Desk Report, 1969; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1969; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - Art Rental - Geico C. Correspondence, 1970; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - Art Rental Policy, 1970; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 77)
  - Art Rental Reports, 1970; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 78)
  - Sales Desk Report, 1970; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 79)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1970; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 80)
  - Art Rental, Miscellaneous, 1971; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 81)
  - Sales Desk Reports, 1971; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 82)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1971; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 83)
  - Art Rental - Clarence Carter Mandala, 1972; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 84)
  - Art Rental - Ledger Sheets, 1972; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 85)
  - Art Rental - Receipts, Miscellaneous, 1972; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 86)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1972; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 87)
  - Art Rental - Clarence Carter Mandala, 1973; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 88)
  - Art Rental - HOM Gallery Inc., 1973; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 89)
  - Art Rental - Kraushaar Galleries, 1973; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 90)
  - Art Rental - Termination of Rental Gallery, 1973; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 91)
  - Art Rental - Miscellaneous, 1973; Series 12 (Box 19, Folder 92)